gearidevices-logoUntitled-1

    * [New
        
        Instinct](https://store.idevicesinc.com/instinct/)

* EXPERIENCE

Hubbell Incorporated Privacy Policy
===================================

_Last Updated: June 8, 2019_

Hubbell Incorporated, located at 40 Waterview Drive, Shelton, Connecticut 06484, and its divisions, subsidiaries, and affiliates are committed to protecting the privacy of our users. This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding our collection, use, and disclosure of the information that you submit to us and that we collect from you through our Website and Mobile Apps. **By visiting the Websites, or by downloading or using our Mobile Apps, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

**As Hubbell Incorporated is a U.S.-headquartered company, your Personal Information will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By submitting your Personal Information, you consent to transfer and processing.**

Whenever we use the words "we" or "us" or "Hubbell Incorporated," we are referring to Hubbell Incorporated and its divisions, subsidiaries, and affiliates. Whenever we use the words "our Websites," we are referring to [www.hubbell.com](http://www.hubbell.com/) and all websites of Hubbell Incorporated and its divisions, subsidiaries and affiliates, as applicable. The mobile applications that are covered by this Privacy Policy include all mobile applications of Hubbell Incorporated and its divisions, subsidiaries and affiliates, as applicable (collectively “Mobile Apps”).

This Privacy Policy is subject to revision and changes, which will be noted here. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy as well as our [Terms of Use](https://idevicesinc.com/terms/) . All defined terms in the Privacy Policy have the same meaning as defined in the Terms of Use unless otherwise noted.

**Personal Information**

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” is information about you that is linked to you as an individual, such as your name, postal address, email address, phone number, credit card number and expiration date, as well as other non-public information that is associated with that information. Personal Information does not include technical information, such as unique device identifiers, randomly assigned unique identifiers in cookies, mobile device name, timestamp, or IP addresses.

**Collection, Storage, and Use in the United States**

Our Websites and Mobile Apps are operated from within the United States, and by submitting your Personal Information to us, either through our Websites, Mobile Apps, or by other means, you are agreeing to the collection, usage, and storage of your Personal Information in the United States as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that your Personal Information may be used by us in the country where it was collected, as well as in the United States, where laws regarding the use of Personal Information may be less strict than the laws in your country.

**How We Collect Personal Information**

We collect Personal Information to better tailor the features, performance and support of our products, services, Websites, and Mobile Apps, and to offer you additional information about our products and services. We collect Personal Information as follows:

* When you voluntarily provide it to us
* When you register and set up an account
* When you sign up to receive emails or other communications
* When you make purchases
* When you participate in surveys, studies, or market research initiatives
* When you communicate with us
* When you consent to receive text messages, we collect your mobile telephone number, in order to send you the text messages
* When you contact us offline or submit information to us offline
* When you visit or otherwise interact with our Websites
* When you download or use our Mobile Apps
* By obtaining it from publicly available sources
* By purchasing or otherwise obtaining it from third parties

**How We Use Personal Information**

Hubbell Incorporated may use the Personal Information we collect to:

* communicate with you and respond to your requests;
* provide, operate, develop, improve, maintain, and protect our programs, products, services and content;
* conduct analysis of usage trends;
* conduct voluntary surveys, studies, or market research initiatives in order to gather feedback about the Websites and Mobile Apps as well as opinions on important issues. When participating in a Hubbell Incorporated survey, study, or market research initiative, we may ask you to submit Personal Information. Such Personal Information is not used for sales solicitations and will not be shared with third parties without your consent or as otherwise permitted by this Privacy Policy;
* support the safety and security of our services;
* authenticate users and to prevent fraud or other unauthorized or illegal activity;
* personalize and target content, including ads;
* enforce our Terms of Use and Privacy Statement and other rules about your use of the Websites and Mobile Apps;
* protect Hubbell Incorporated’s rights or property and/or the rights of others;
* comply with laws or regulations, court orders or other legal process;
* create De-identified Information. We may create “De-identified Information” from Personal Information by excluding data (such as your name or email address) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. There are no restrictions to the way Hubbell Incorporated can use or share De-identified Information.

**Our Disclosure of Your Personal Information**

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, or share your Personal Information with third parties. We disclose your Personal Information for the following purposes:

* _Providing Services to You, Fulfilling Orders, and Maintaining Systems._ We may share information about you with third parties who perform services on our behalf, who provide content through our Services, and with others to enable services and functionality and to perform maintenance and improve the services.

When you purchase a product or a service from us, we will share select Personal Information, such as your shipping address and billing address, with third-party fulfillment companies in the United States, in order to deliver the product or service to you. We may also share your Personal Information with third-party service providers in the United States that provide advertising and marketing services for us, including distribution of postal mail, electronic alerts, email and mobile text messages to our customers and potential customers. We require these third-party service providers to refrain from using your Personal Information, except to provide the services requested by us. To opt-out of being included in information that Hubbell Incorporated provides to third parties for advertising and marketing purposes, please see the How You Can Stop Receiving Marketing Communications section of this Privacy Policy.

We also hire vendors that work on our systems that may have access to your Personal Information in the course of performing their duties. We require those vendors to keep your Personal Information confidential and not to use it for their own purposes.

You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Information with our third-party service providers and vendors.

* _Sharing with Affiliates._ We reserve the right to share some or all of your Personal Information with our subsidiaries, joint ventures, and other companies under our common control (collectively, "Affiliates"), for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

* _Compliance with Laws and Protection of Rights._ Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Information, we may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with laws or regulations court orders, subpoenas or other legal process; or (b) protect and defend our rights or property, or the rights or safety of third parties, or to enforce our Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy.

* _Acquisition, Sale, or Reorganization._ We may also use and disclose Personal Information in connection with a contemplated reorganization or an actual reorganization of our business, in connection with financing, a sale or other transaction involving the disposal of all or part of our business or assets, including for the purpose of permitting the due diligence required to decide whether to proceed with a transaction. If the sale occurs, the purchaser will be entitled to use and disclose the Personal Information collected by us, and the purchaser will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Advertising**

* _Interest-Based Advertising_ . We may use "interest-based" advertisements also known as "online behavioral advertising." Online behavioral advertising is advertising that is directed to you based, at least in part, on your Internet browsing behavior across websites and over time. Although we do not share Personal Information with the third parties that conduct interest-based advertising operations on our behalf, these third parties and their affiliates do collect certain information as a result of their javascript "tags" and other technologies being used on our Websites. The information that they collect includes the names of web pages you view (URL's), unique identifiers, your IP address, timestamp, and certain types of technical information. A longer list of some of the technologies used for advertising and other purposes on our Websites and in our Mobile Apps are listed under the "Technologies Used" section.

* _Third Parties May Collect Personal Information from Other Sources_ . Some third parties involved in advertising operations may maintain their own proprietary consumer databases that allow them to personally identify or track website visitors. Other third parties have proprietary technologies to determine what additional devices you may use, on which it can display relevant advertisements.

* _Do-Not-Track._ Do-Not-Track is a public-private initiative that has developed a “flag” or signal that an Internet user may activate in the user’s browser software to notify websites that the user does not wish to be “tracked” by third-parties as defined by the initiative. The online community has not agreed on what actions, if any, should be taken by the websites that receive the “do-not-track” signal, and therefore Do-Not-Track is not yet standardized. Our website does not alter its behavior or change its services when it receives a “do-not-track” flag or signal from your browser.

* _Your Privacy and Ad Choices._ You can make decisions about your privacy and the ads you receive. You can control whether companies serve you on-line behavioral advertising by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance website and using its opt-out: [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) . The DAA opt-out requires that cookies not be blocked in your browser.

As an alternative to the DAA opt–out, you can also elect to block browser cookies from first parties (such as those from our website) and browser cookies from third parties (such as advertisers) by using the cookie blocking options built into your browser software. If you block browser cookies, some parts of our website may not function correctly. Also, blocking cookies will not stop third-parties from collecting IP address, data stored in "Flash" cookies, and certain other types of technical information that may uniquely identify your browser.

**Technologies Used**

Third parties, widgets, and hosted solutions that we may use on our website may use the following technologies for features, services, advertising, or analytics:

* _Browser cookies._ Browser cookies are small pieces data placed on your computer as you navigate websites with your browser. Browser cookies allow websites and various third-parties to distinguish your device from others by having the cookie consist of a unique identifier or other data. Cookies can have many uses, such as to target advertising as well as to enable website functionality and for security. We use both session cookies (which expire after you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. (Each browser is different, so check the "help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Hubbell Incorporated products or services that require you to "sign in", and some areas of our website may not work properly, and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings.

* _Local shared objects._ Local shared objects (such as "Flash" cookies) are associated with non-Browser software like Flash Player. Local shared objects can be used like cookies to distinguish your device from others but will not be deleted or blocked using browser cookie controls. You can visit adobe.com for guidance on how to delete and block Flash cookies.

* _HTML5 local storage_ . HTML5 local storage is another way that browsers can distinguish your device from others as well as remember data that may be important for the functioning of the website. Typically HTML5 local storage is only deleted if all Internet history, cache, and cookies are deleted. You should check your browser software for how to delete HTML5 local storage in your particular case.

* _Web beacons._ Web beacons are image files that are used by third-party advertisers, analytics companies, and others. Web beacons are embedded in web pages you visit and cause your browser to share its IP address with the third-party source of the beacon, together with any cookies associated with that third-party. Web beacons can be used with or without cookies. Blocking cookies will not stop your IP address from being shared through the use of beacons.

* _E-tags._ E-tags are used to prevent duplicative downloading of content to your browser, which can enhance browser performance. E-tags use unique identifiers for content that can also be used to distinguish your browser in certain instances from others. Typically e-tags are only deleted if all Internet history, cache, and cookies are deleted. You should check your browser software for how to delete e-tags in your particular case.

* _Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer and mobile device_ . Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Websites, we may automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave one of our Websites. We also receive the Internet protocol (“IP”) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system, type of web browser you are using, email patterns, information regarding your mobile device (including UDID) and mobile operating system (if you are accessing the Websites using a mobile device), as well as the name of your ISP or your mobile carrier. We may also receive location data passed to us from third-party services or GPS-enabled devices that you have enabled. Also, as described in this Privacy Policy, we may receive information when you access Third-Party Sites through the Service.

* We use Hotjar in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on [this link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy).  
    You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this [opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).

Our Mobile Apps may use the following technologies for features, services, advertising, or analytics:

* Collection of device identifiers, such as Android ID and MAC address
* Collection of geolocation, including precise geolocation
* Device name
* Collection of platform specific identifiers such as Apple's Identifier for Advertising and Identifier for Vendor, and Android ID or Android's advertising identifier
* Collection of carrier-related information including the name of your wireless carrier, and IDs related to the cell phone hardware in your phone as well as the network to which the device is connected
* IP address
* Mobile phone number
* App-specific and instance-specific identifiers

_Other technologies_ . Our Websites and Mobile Apps may occasionally use other technologies both for purposes of advertising as well as for features, analytics, and services.

**Social Network Widgets**

Our Websites or Mobile Apps may include social network sharing widgets that may provide information to their associated social networks or third parties about your interactions with our web pages that you visit, even if you do not click on or otherwise interact with the plug-in or widget. Information is transmitted from your browser and may include an identifier assigned by the social network or third party, information about your browser type, operating system, device type, IP address, and the URL of the web page where widget appears. If you use social network tools or visit social networking sites, you should read their privacy disclosures, to learn what information they collect, use, and share.

**How You Can Stop Receiving Marketing Communications**

We respect your communication preferences, and you may opt-out of receiving certain communications for marketing purposes sent by Hubbell Incorporated or sent by third parties on behalf of Hubbell Incorporated. When you receive sales flyers, advertisements, direct mail, and other promotional communications from us, including e-mail, you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in the email you receive, or by contacting us directly using the [Contact Us Form](https://www.hubbell.com/contactUs). Once you have submitted your email address to "unsubscribe," please note that you may continue to receive emails for a time while our system updates your request. On our Websites and certain of our Mobile Apps, you may change any of your Personal Information by logging into your account and editing your information. Regardless of recorded opt-out preferences, Hubbell Incorporated reserves the right to send emails or other communications for administrative or transactional purposes, including, but not limited to, communications related to the maintenance of your account and software or product updates.

**Information from Children Under 13**

This website is not intentionally designed for or directed at children under 13 years of age. We do not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under 13 years of age. Please contact Hubbell Incorporated using this [Contact Us Form](https://www.hubbell.com/contactUs) if you think we may have inadvertently collected such information, and we will attempt to delete the information.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our Websites or Mobile Apps may provide a link or otherwise provide access to another website, mobile application, or Internet location (collectively “Third-Party Sites”). We provide these links merely for your convenience, and we do not endorse Third-Party Sites, their contents, or any goods or services available through the Third-Party Sites. We have no control over, do not review, and are not responsible for Third-Party Sites, their content, or any goods or services available through the Third-Party Sites. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to Third-Party Sites, and any information you provide to Third-Party Sites, you provide at your own risk.

Any information you share with Third-Party Sites through the Service may be collected by Hubbell Incorporated. We will use such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Security**

We implement technical, administrative, and organizational safeguards to prevent access to your Personal Information by unauthorized persons. You should know, however, that we cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with the storage and transmission of Personal Information.

**Google Drive™ API**

The iDevices Connected App on the Google Play store uses the Google Drive API to enable user customization of the app with the user’s own custom images for their home and devices. The user grants iDevices the right to store custom images they uploaded with the Connected App to their Google Drive account. Then access it for display on app render. At no time does iDevices share or use the user’s data for any other purpose.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes, and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To exercise your rights, you may make one request each year by contacting us using the [Contact Us Form](https://www.hubbell.com/contactUs) with a "Request for California Privacy Information" on the subject line or in the body of your message. Be sure to provide in the request sufficient information to properly identify you and/or the members of your family.

**How You Can Reach Us**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or to opt-out of receiving information as permitted under this Privacy Policy, please contact us using our [Contact Us Form](https://www.hubbell.com/contactUs) or by writing to use at:  
  
Hubbell Incorporated  
40 Waterview Drive  
Shelton, CT 06484-1000 Attn: Hubbell Website

**How to Request Access to, or the Correction of, Your Personal Information**

Except in limited circumstances governed by law, you may obtain access to and have your Personal Information in our records corrected. A request for access or correction must be made using our [Contact Us Form](https://www.hubbell.com/contactUs) or by writing to us at:  
  
Hubbell Incorporated  
40 Waterview Drive  
Shelton, CT 06484-1000 Attn: Hubbell Website

[Where To Buy

Buy iDevices products at a local retailer near you.](https://idevicesinc.com/where-to-buy/)

[iDevices Pro

Broaden your portfolio and increase your bottom line.](https://idevicesinc.com/pro/)

Stay Connected

  I agree to the terms of Hubbell’s [privacy policy](https://www.hubbell.com/hubbell/en/terms-of-use?__hstc=11068263.6ec8c4c76d5224ffbc8afea699e6dc70.1610035734447.1636376101508.1636472790961.48&__hssc=11068263.12.1636659361358&__hsfp=3003510332#99) and for my personal data to be processed to be contacted by Hubbell.

 iDevices Products

 Experience

 Company

 Support

© 2024 iDevices, LLC. All Rights Reserved. iDevices and Sweetblue are trademarks owned by iDevices, LLC. Apple, the Apple logo, iPad, iPhone, and iPod Touch are trademarks of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries. App Store is a service mark of Apple Inc. The Bluetooth® word mark and logos are registered trademarks owned by Bluetooth SIG, Inc. and any use of such marks by iDevices, LLC is under license. [TERMS OF USE](https://idevicesinc.com/terms/)  |  [PRIVACY POLICY](https://idevicesinc.com/privacy/)  |  [TERMS OF SALE](https://idevicesinc.com/terms-of-sale/)

[](https://www.hubbell.com/)iDevices is a proud member of the Hubbell family.
